Luyện Thị Việt Chinh Interpreter

(S) 0354910863

chinhvcu97@gmail.com

http://fb.com/chinhxubi

(a) Female

(m) 8/10/1997

(P) Hà Nội



Occupation Goals

As a fiercely ambitious young girl, i prematurely set up my both short term and long term goals in order to clearly determine which direction i should follow and what i should do. For short term goal, i ask myself to get soft and hard skills, knowledge and other must - have skills continuously improved. Those seeds will gradually grow up, eventually lead to reinforcing my long term goals that encompass becoming a seasoned specialist in some area more importantly related to English, shaping up my own career following by Passion - Enthusiasm - Inovation.



Education

THƯƠNG MAI UNIVERSITY

BUSINESS ENGLISH DEGREE

I attended Thuong Mai University 4 years ago from 2015-2019, in which i specialized in Business English that virtually encompasses the overall of Business Industry, UK AND US cultures, interpretation and and translation skills. Those knowledges intentionally served for my english improvement, business savvy and other necessary skills that had gradually created a solid background for my real foretaste of life without any question.



Work Experience

AMACCAO GROUP

27/09/2019 - now

9/2015 - hiện tại

Assistant plus Translator

Now i am an office staff working as an interpretation assistant for two Canadian managers from Amaccao Group- a multi-sector company. This job requires me to show my organizing an communication skills as what i mainly do is to organize the schedules for the two Canadian managers and attending their meetings with Vietnamese or foreign customers/partners for translation. In the last one year involved in this sector, i have found myself more confident, active and influent in my Language skill.

As the job is an other part related to presenting, my presentation skill has been enhanced in the process of delivering and convincing the listeners to any topic. Therefore, i am quite confident and not mind being in charge of presentation if needed.

HANOIRESIDENCE AGENT

2/1/2019 - 30/7/2019

Sales-staff

i was mainly in charge of marketing, selling and promoting our regularly updated properties whose potential customers were mostly world-wide expats working and staying in Ha Noi. As a main part of my job, i regularly showed available properties in the area of ha noi to the international customers, whose typical requirements and tastes were organically approached, thoroughly explored by my own marketing strategies beforehand, and devotedly supported as well as took thorough care of them in terms of finding, negotiating and eventually closing the deal in order to find out a ticking - all - boxes apartment or house . As a result, that daily basis work have unintentionally enhanced my customer care skill, communication and negotiation skills, confidence, learning how to read and listening to customers'mind which are must - have skills for anyone greatly desiring to contribute to and get promoted in this cut - throat business world. Regardless of its pressure and hardship, i had never minded getting my hands dirty or working my butt off with a trifecta notion of Determination - Harship - Enthusiasm.

ETHNIC TRAVEL

1/12/2016 - 30/11/2018

Tour guide

I have been working as a tour guide for almost 2 years, in which i was in charge of guiding western tourists to the

northern sightseeing places such as Ninh Binh, Ha Long Bay, Bai Tu Long Bay,... This job required me to dynamically arrange things and resolve unexpected issues in order to get things done perfectly along with customers' satisfaction, giving me an incredible opportunity to have a real foretaste of tourism industry, learn more about independent work skills, get my soft skill like communication not mentioning public speaking enhanced and most importantly level up my English ability.



Computer and languague skills

Computer skills	I can basically use some computer skills like Microsoft Word and Excel.
Language skills	I am intermediately influent in English skills in terms of speaking, listening, writing and reading. Personally, my English speaking and listening literally surpass other two skills as I have technically had lots of practical chance on those two important skills.